Finding Aid for George Murphy papers, 1911-1961
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
George Murphy papers 1911-1961
Murphy, George, 1897-1961.
86484 Aa 2; AA; UAm
Judge of the Recorder's Court in Detroit and Frank Murphy's brother; contain correspondence, legal briefs, newspaper clippings, and other materials concerning Detroit politics, 1935-1961, the grand jury investigation of Detroit street railways, 1936, arbitration of labor disputes, 1936-1941, investigation of the Charles Street housing project, 1939-1940, as well as materials illuminating the careers and personal affairs of both George and Frank Murphy, especially in relation to Detroit and the Philippine Islands.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
15 linear feet
1 volumes
1 oversize folders
The collection was the gift of the estate of the Hon. George Murphy (donor no. 3074 ) and came to the library in 1965.
Researchers must sign the Murphy contract before access to the papers will be permitted.
George Ignatius Murphy was born January 20,1894, at Harbor Beach, Michigan, to John T. and Mary (Brennan) Murphy. He attended the University of Michigan where he received the A.B. degree in 1917 and the LL.B degree in 1922. While at the University he joined the Sigma Chi fraternity and served on the University's world record breaking two-mile relay track team. During both World Wars he served in the United States Naval Air Corps. During the years of peace, he served in the Naval Reserves. He entered private law practice with his brother, Frank, and Edward Kemp in the early 1930's and served as assistant attorney general of Michigan from 1932 to 1934 and as judge of the Recorder's Court in Detroit from 1935 to 1961. Long active in Democratic Party affairs, Murphy was a delegate to the 1924 Democratic National Convention, and ran at various times for prosecuting attorney of Huron County, for Wayne County Circuit Court commissioner, and for state senator from Wayne County. In 1932 he became state chairman of the Veteran's Division of the Democratic Party, In 1946 he married Brigid McKenna; they had two children., Frances Anastasia born in 1950 and Marguerite Mavoureen born in 1952. Murphy died in Detroit, July 11, 1961.
The George Murphy papers, which encompass the years 1911 to 1961, are most comprehensive for the decade following 1932. During this period - the most politically active in Murphy's career - the correspondence is especially useful in illustrating George Murphy's role in his brother's emergence as a politician, especially his role as dispenser of patronage in the depression years. The papers, of course, illuminate the social function performed by the Recorder's Court and contain voluminous correspondence with state and federal judges, attorneys, prisoners, prison officials, probation officers, etc. Judge Murphy also maintained close contact with affairs in his home town, Harbor Beach. Included in the collection are significant materials on affairs in the Philippines during his brother's governorship there, particularly correspondence during the years 1933 to 1936 with his sister, Marguerite, Eleanor Bumgardner, and with leading Filipinos concerning conditions there.
Subjects:
African Americans--Michigan.; Courts--Michigan.; Democratic Party (Mich.); Depressions--1929--Michigan--Detroit.; Detroit (Mich.); Detroit (Mich.). Recorder's Court.; Housing.; Labor--Michigan.; Michigan--Politics and government--1929-1938.; Michigan--Politics and government--1939-1945.; Michigan--Politics and government--1946-1960.; Michigan--Politics and government--1961-1970.; Michigan--Politics and government--1837-1950.; Michigan--Politics and government--1951-; Murphy, George, 1897-1961.; Philippines--History--1898-1946.; Presidents--United States--Election--1932.; Public welfare--Michigan--Detroit.; Street-railroads--Michigan--Detroit.; Sit-down strikes--Michigan.; United States--Politics and government--1933-1945.; United States--Politics and government--1929-1933.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Aguinaldo, Emilio, 1869-1964.; Moody, Blair, 1902-1954.; Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.; Philippines--History--1898-1946.
Contributors:
Abbott, Horatio J. (Horatio Johnson), 1876-1936; Aguinaldo, Emilio, 1869-1964.; Black, Eugene F., 1903-1990; Black, Hugo LaFayette, 1886-1971.; Bowles, Charles, 1884-1957.; Brennan, William J. (William Joseph), 1906-1997.; Brown, Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald), 1905-1996.; Brown, Prentiss M. (Prentiss Marsh), 1889-1973.; Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.; Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925.; Bumgardner, Eleanor M. (Eleanor Margaret); Bushnell, George E. (George Edward), 1887-1965.; Carr, Lowell Juilliard, 1885-; Cobo, Albert E. (Albert Eugene), 1893-1957.; Comstock, William Alfred, 1877-1949.; Coughlin, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1891-1979.; Couzens, Frank, 1902-1950.; Cramton, Louis C. (Louis Convers), b. 1875.; Cromwell, James Henry Roberts.; Cunningham, Leon Max, d. 1930.; Darrow, Clarence, 1857-1938.; Davis, John W. (John William), 1873-1955.; De Maggio, Andrew.; Dethmers, John R., 1903-1971.; Dewey, John, 1859-1952.; Dingell, John D. (John David), 1894-1955.; Douglas, William O. (William Orville), 1898-1980.; Edwards, George, 1914-; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969.; Eliasohn, Jack, 1908-; Farley, James A. (James Aloysius), 1888-1976.; Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.; Ford, Henry, 1917-1987.; Foy, Byron Cecil, 1893-1970.; Frankensteen, Richard T. (Richard Truman), 1907-1977; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965.; Fulbright, J. William (James William), 1905-1995.; Garner, John Nance, 1868-1967.; Gillein, Hilmer.; Gomon, Josephine Fellows, 1892-1975.; Green, Fred W. (Fred Warren), 1872-1936.; Griffiths, Hicks G., 1910-; Hannah, John A., 1902-1991; Harding, Ann, 1904-1981.; Hart, Philip A. (Philip Aloysius), 1912-1976.; Hatcher, Harlan, 1898-1998.; Hayden, Joseph Ralston, 1887-1945.; Hill, Norman Llewellyn, 1895-; Hoover, J. Edgar (John Edgar), 1895-1972.; Howe, Louis McHenry, 1871-1936.; Jayne, Ira Waite, 1882-; Jeffries, Edward, 1900-1950; Kelly, Harry F. (Harry Francis), 1895-1971.; Kemp, Edward Gearing, 1887-1962.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963.; Kennedy, Joseph P. (Joseph Patrick), 1888-1969.; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968.; Larned, Abner E.; Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963.; Levin, Saul R.; Lewis, John Llewellyn, 1880-1969.; Lincoln, Burr, 1880-1937.; Louis, Joe, 1914-1981.; Lowery, Percival C., 1885-1978.; McAllister, Thomas Raymond, 1905-; MacArthur, Jean Faircloth.; McNamara, Patrick Vincent, 1894-1966.; Madrigal, Pacita.; Martel, Frank Xavier, 1888-; Mead, Harry L., 1893-; Miriani, Louis C.; Moley, Raymond L., 1886-; Moody, Blair, 1902-1954.; Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.; Murphy, Irene Ellis, 1900-; Murphy, Marguerite.; Osmeña, Sergio, 1878-1961.; Parker, Frank, 1872-1947.; Picard, Frank A., 1889-1963.; Pollock, James K. (James Kerr), 1898-1968; Potter, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1916-1979.; Quezon, Manuel Luis, 1878-1944.; Quirino, Elpidio, 1890-1956.; Rabaut, Louis Charles, 1886-1961.; Reuther, Walter, 1907-1970.; Romulo, Carlos P. (Carlos Peña), 1899-1985.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Roosevelt, James, 1907-1991; Rutledge, Wiley Blount, 1894-1949.; Smith, Gerald L. K. (Gerald Lyman Kenneth), 1898-1976; Smith, Talbot.; Staebler, Neil, 1905-2000; Sugar, Maurice, 1891-1974.; Swainson, John B. (John Burley), 1925-1994.; Voelker, John D. (John Donaldson), 1903-1991; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.; Tuttle, Arthur J., 1868-1944.; Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.; Van Wagoner, Murray Delos, 1898-; Waite, John Barker, 1882-1967; Walker, Moses L.; Warren, Earl, 1891-1974.; Whittaker, Alfred Heacock, 1894-; Williams, G. Mennen, 1911-1988.; Williams, G. Mennen, Mrs.; Yost, Fielding Harris, 1871-1946.
Genre Terms:
Drawings.; Oral histories.; Photographs.
- Correspondence and other papers 1911-1961
  - Undated 1911-1931, 35 folders (Box 1)
  - 1932, 11 folders (Box 2)
  - 1932 memorandums and correspondence from Democratic National Committee (Box 2)
  - 1932 legal correspondence and miscellaneous briefs (Box 2)
  - 1933, 10 folders (Box 2)
  - 1932-1933 Applications and recommendations (Box 2)
  - January 1934-April 1935, 15 folders (Box 3)
  - May 1935-April 1936, 28 folders (Box 4)
  - May 1936-July 1937, 37 folders (Box 5)
  - August 1937-November 1938, 37 folders (Box 6)
  - December 1938-January 1940, 27 folders (Box 7)
  - February 1940-March 1941, 21 folders (Box 8)
  - April 1941-September 1946, 27 folders (Box 9)
  - October 1946-December 1951, 28 folders (Box 10)
  - January 1952-December 1955, 20 folders (Box 11)
  - January 1956-June 1959, 19 folders (Box 12)
  - July 1959-August 1961 and later undated, 22 folders (Box 13)
  - 1961 funeral miscellanea (Box 13)
- Law and politics 1926-1952
  - Legal briefs 1926 (Box 14)
  - Legal briefs 1932 (Box 14)
  - Labor arbitration materials 1952, undated (Box 14)
  - Charles Street Housing Project 1939-1940 (Box 14)
    (see also Correspondence series for additional materials)
  - Detroit Street Railways, grand jury investigations, etc. 1936-1941 (Box 14)
    (reports and miscellaneous)
- Personal 1922-1959
  - Correspondence with brother Frank Murphy 1941-1946, 6 folders (Box 15)
  - Military service undated, 1943-1944, 6 folders (Box 15)
  - Clippings 1922 (Box 15)
  - Clippings 1923 (Box 15)
  - Clippings 1931-1935 (Box 15)
  - Clippings 1936-1940 (Box 15)
  - Clippings 1951 (Box 15)
  - Clippings undated, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Scrapbook (Box 15)
  - Miscellanea undated, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Papers 1959 concerning campaigns for re-election as Recorder's Court judge (Box 15)
  - Student notebook circa 1920 (Box 15)
  - Photographs of Murphy with his brother Frank, and with other notables, such as Emilio Aguinaldo and Blair Moody (Box 15)
    (See also oversize folder UAm)
  - Transcript of interview with George Murphy conducted by Sidney Fine and Robert M. Warner March 28, 1957 (Volume 1)
    (interview concerns the Flint Sit-Down strike and the career of his brother Frank Murphy)
Selective Index to Correspondents
Abbott, Horatio J. (Horatio Johnson), 1876-
1920's and 1930's
Aguinaldo, Emilio, 1869-1964.
Apr. 11, 1935
Black, Eugene F., 1903-
June 30, 1958, July 16, 1958, May 6, 1959
Black, Hugo LaFayette, 1886-1971.
Mar. 11, 1952, June 5, 1953 (secretary)
Bowles, Charles, 1884-1957.
June 7, 1930, June 10, 1930, June 24, 1930, June 28, 1930, July 2, 1930
Brennan, William J. (William Joseph), 1906-1997.
Oct. 22, 1956, Sept. 13, 1957
Brown, Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald), 1905-1996.
July 2, 1958
Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889-1973.
Aug. 13, 1935, Aug. 6, 1935 with Frank Martel about Frank Murphy's candidacy for governor; Jan. 24, 1938, Feb. 28, 1938, Mar. 18, 1939, Nov. 7, 1939, Jan. 4, 1940, May 27, 1940, June 12, 1940, May 27, 1941, Nov. 24, 1951, Dec. 29, 1941
Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.
May 1, 1930, June 6, 1930, Aug. 6, 1931
Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925.
Mar. 11, 1920, Dec. 8, 1920, 1921, Dec. 30, 1922
Bumgardner, Eleanor M. (Eleanor Margaret)
1933-1949
Bushnell, George E. (George Edward), 1887-1965.
Apr. 23, 1926, Jan. 22, 1952, Feb. 11, 1952
Carr, Lowell Juilliard, b. 1885.
May 1, 1953
Cobo, Albert Eugene, 1893-1957.
June 22, 1951, Aug. 25, 1954
Comstock, William Alfred, 1877-1949.
Nov. 11, 1932, Nov. 10, 1932, Nov. 12, 1932
Coughlin, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1891-1979.
Mar. 6, 1933, July 7, 1933, Sept. 19, 1933, Sept. 20, 1933, Sept. 20, 1933, Feb. 1, 1934, Feb. 27, 1936 (Frank Murphy to Coughlin), Sept. 21, 1939 (Coughlin to Mrs. R. R. Cockburn), Apr. 4, 1944 and undated
Couzens, Frank, 1902-1950.
June 10, 1931 and scattered
Cramton, Louis C. (Louis Convers), b. 1875.
Jan. 1954
Cromwell, James Henry Roberts.
Late 1930's-1954. Letters Oct. -Nov. 1954 concerning the Dodge estate. Cromwell was one-time United States Consul in Canada, later joined Washington law firm
Cunningham, Leon Max, d. 1930.
1927-1930
Darrow, Clarence, 1857-1938.
Mar. 3, 1932, Sept. 7, 1933, Sept. 8, 1933, Oct. 25, 1933, Apr. 23, 1935, Sept. 30, 1935, (Mrs. C.), Jan. 2, 1941 (Mrs. C.), Jan. 20, 1941 (Mrs. C.), Feb. 12, 1941
Davis, John W. (John William), 1873-1955.
June 3, 1932, June 16, 1932
De Maggio, Andrew.
1940's and 1950's
Dethmers, John R., 1903-1971.
Nov. 3, 1959, Feb. 8, 1961
Dewey, John, 1859-1952.
Jan. 15, 1931
Dingell, John D. (John David), 1894-1955.
1930's - 1950's
Douglas, William O. (William Orville), 1898-1980.
Feb. 28, 1952, Apr. 18, 1955, Feb. 16, 1959, May 5, 1959
Edwards, George, 1914-
June 20, 1957, Feb. 17, 1959, May 19, 1959, Aug. 7, 1959, Sept. 1, 1959, Sept. 21, 1960, Apr. 12, 1961, July 2l, 1961
Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969.
Dec. 12, 1960, Jan. 3, 1961
Eliasohn, Jack, 1908-
Throughout on his position on the Michigan Parole Board
Farley, James Aloysius, 1888-
Mar. 17, 1932, Mar. 28, 1932, Mar. 29, 1932, Mar. 30, 1932, Apr. 1, 1932, Apr. 2, 1932, Apr. 11, 1932, Apr. 12, 1932, Apr. 13, 1932, Apr. 14, 1932, Apr. 16, 1932, Apr. 21, 1932, Apr. 23, 1932, Apr. 26, 1932, Apr. 28, 1932, May 3, 1932, May 4, 1932, May 9, 1932, Aug. 29, 1932, Sept. 15, 1932, Sept. 17, 1932, Sept. 19, 1932, Nov. 15, 1932, Nov. 28, 1932
May 16, 1933, May 29, 1933, June 17, 1933, June 22, 1933, Mar. 18, 1936, May 22, 1936, May 23, 1936, Aug. 29, 1936, Sept. 10, 1936, Feb. 3, 1937, Mar. 1, 1937, Apr. 30, 1937, May 4, 1937, Dec. 7, 1937, Mar. 11, 1938, Sept. 30, 1932 (to Farley from M. Scott)
Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.
Dec. 7, 1942, Nov. 10, 1952, Jan. 5, 1959
Ford, Henry, 1917-1987.
May 16, 1953
Foy, Byron Cecil, 1893-1970.
Throughout
Frankensteen, Richard T., 1907-
Dec. 30, 1938, Feb. 7, 1941, Sept. 9, 1941
Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965.
May 30, 1941
Fulbright, J. William (James William), 1905-1995.
Mar. 24, 1958
Garner, John Nance, 1868-1967.
Jan. 14, 1936
Gillein, Hilmer.
1930's and 1940's
Gomon, Josephine Fellows, 1892-1975.
1930's and 1940's
Green, Fred Warren, 1872-1936.
June 8, 1928, July 2, 1928, July 6, 1928
Griffiths, Hicks G., 1910-
1950's
Hannah, John A., 1902-
Oct. 21, 1960
Harding, Ann, 1904-1981.
Apr. 1, 1927, Oct. 8, 1931, Oct. 3, 1932, Nov. 29, 1933, Aug. 31, 1933, Dec. 29, 1934, Apr. 29, 1935, July 12, 1935, May 5, 1936 and Nov. 9, 1931 (Harding to Hoover [copy])
Hart, Philip A. (Philip Aloysius), 1912-1976.
Sept. 28, 1959, Nov. 16, 1959, Dec. 11, 1959, Jan. 5, 1960, Mar. 7, 1961, Apr. 13, 1961
Hatcher, Harlan Henthorne, 1898-
Apr. 19, 1954, Mar. 3, 1959, Sept. 29, 1960, May 8, 1961
Hayden, Joseph Ralston, 1887-1945.
May 9, 1939
Hill, Norman Llewellyn, 1895-
Throughout
Hoover, J. Edgar (John Edgar), 1895-1972.
Feb, 1, 1939, Aug. 25, 1939, Mar 11, 1940, Apr. 18, 1940, Sept. 27, 1940, June 30, 1941, Sept. 20,1941, Feb. 21, 1942
Howe, Louis McHenry, 1871-1936.
Jan. 20, 1932, Feb. 9, 1932, Feb. 10, 1932, Feb. 15, 1932, Oct. 19, 1932, Oct. 21, 1932, Oct. 24, 1932, Oct. 31, 1932, Aug. 6, 1935
Jayne, Ira Waite, 1882-
business affairs scattered throughout collection
Jeffries, Edward, 1900-
1940's
Kelly, Harry F. (Harry Francis), 1895-1971.
Jan, 19, 1940, Feb. 22, 1940, Apr. 12, 1941, Sept. 3, 1941, May 8, 1953, May 25, 1954, Oct. 11, 1960, July 11, 1961
Kemp, Edward Gearing, 1887-1962.
1923-1954
Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963.
Oct. 14, 1958, Aug. 23, 1960
Kennedy, Joseph P. (Joseph Patrick), 1888-1969.
Oct. 12, 1937, Dec. 11, 1937, June 14, 1948
Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968.
Mar. 14, 1961
Larned, Abner E.
W.P.A, and applications for jobs in the 1930's
Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963.
Sept. 19, 1950
Levin, Saul R.
1950's
Lewis, John Llewellyn, 1880-1969.
Dec. 1, 1938, Mar. 19, 1958, Oct. 17, 1958
Lincoln, Burr, 1880-1937.
Throughout
Louis, Joe, 1914-1981.
Jan. 4, 1937
Lowery, Percival C., 1885-1978.
1929-1930 and scattered
McAllister, Thomas Raymond, 1905-
Mar. 14, 1939, Apr. 14, 1939, Jan. 28, 1941, Nov. 11, 1946, Apr. 28, 1953, June 8, 1953, Jan. 8, 1959, Jan. 23, 1959, Sept. 17, 1959, Aug. 22, 1961
MacArthur, Jean Faircloth.
Mar. 25, 1960, Apr. 11, 1960, Dec. 28, 1960, June 28, 1961
McNamara, Patrick Vincent, 1894-1966.
Apr. 11, 1950, July 6, 1955, Jan. 4, 1956, Sept. 12, 1957, Mar. 13, 1958, Mar. 21, 1958, Jan. 13, 1959, Oct. 15, 1959, Feb. 4, 1960
Madrigal, Pacita.
1935-1958
Martel, Frank Xavier, 1888-
1945-1961
Mead, Harry L., 1893-
1930's and 1960
Miriani, Louis C.
Oct. 23, 1950, May 19, 1953, Dec. 10, 1959
Moley, Raymond L., 1886-
Dec. 19, 1934
Moody, Blair, 1902-1954.
Apr. 11, 1952, May 26, 1952, Nov. 28, 1952
Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.
1911, 1917-1918, 1920, 1922, 1925, 1928, 1931, 1933-1936, 1949
Murphy, Irene Ellis, 1900-
1934 and 1950's
Murphy, Marguerite.
1933-1936 and scattered into the 1950's
Osmeña, Sergio, 1989-1961
Dec. 20, 1937
Parker, Frank, 1872-1947.
Aug. 5, 1935, Dec. 21, 1941, June 21, 1941 (Mrs.)
Picard, Frank A., 1889-1963.
Nov. 19, 1932, Apr. 15, 1935, Jun. 14, 1935, Sept. 18, 1935, Feb. 15, 1936, Feb. 18, 1936, Feb. 21, 1936, Feb. 5, 1937, Feb. 6, 1937, Feb. 11, 1937, May 13, 1937, May 18, 1937, May 21, 1937, May 28, 1937, Oct. 20, 1937, Sept. 23, 1938, Mar. 17, 1939, Apr. 9, 1941, Apr. 9, 1941, Feb. 6, 1942, Oct. 24, 1950, Mar. 8, 1954, Oct. 5, 1954, Sept. 29, 1959, June 26, 1961
Pollock, James Kerr, 1898-
Oct. 10, 1940, Oct. 5, 1953
Potter, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1916-1979.
Apr. 15, 1958
Quezon, Manuel Luis, 1878-1944.
Jan. 23, 1934 (telegram) Feb 5 1934, Feb 7, 1934, Feb. 28, 1934, Mar. 1, 1934, Mar. 3, 1934, Mar. 26, 1934, Apr. 4, 1934, Oct. 24, 1934, Nov. 9, 1934, Nov. 10, 1934, Dec. 4, 1934, May 7, 1935, Oct. 25, 1935, Mar. 24, 1934, Mar. 28, 1934, Apr. 4, 1934, Apr. 9, 1934, Apr. 11, 1934, Feb. 14, 1935, Sept. 10, 1936, Aug. 21, 1942, and Nov .22, 1943; and with Jose and Carmen Melencio: Jan, 22, 1934, Jan. 25, 1934, Jan. 29, 1934, Feb. 2, 1934, Feb. 8, 1934, Feb. 15, 1934, Mar. 2, 1934, Mar. 24, 1934, Mar. 28, 1934, Apr. 4, 1934, Apr. 9, 1934, Apr. 11, 1934, and Feb. 14, 1935
Quirino, Elpidio, 1890-1956.
Sept. 28, 1935, Jan. 1, 1936, July 24, 1953
Rabaut, Louis Charles, 1886-1961.
scattered from 1930's on
Reuther, Walter, 1907-1970.
Mar. 4, 1954, May 3, 1955, May 29, 1957, Jan. 28, 1958., Sept. 4, 1958, Oct. 13, 1958, Dec. 4, 1958 (secretary), Dec. 30, 1959, Jan. 7, 1959, Nov. 21, 1960, Apr. 11, 1961, July 20, 1961
Romulo, Carlos P. (Carlos Peña), 1899-1985.
Oct. 25, 1960
Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.
Sept. 3, 1932
Roosevelt, James, 1907-
Feb. 12, 1959, Feb. 24, 1959
Rutledge, Wiley Blount, 1894-1949.
Aug. 11, 1949
Smith, Gerald L. K. (Gerald Lyman Kenneth), 1898-
Mar. 12, 1942
Smith, Talbot.
Aug. 4, 1955, Nov. 17, 1956, Sept. 5, 1958, Dec. 24, 1958, June 1, 1960 and undated
Staebler, Neil, 1905-
May 1, 1957, Jan. 3, 1958, Apr. 1, 1958
Sugar, Maurice, 1891-1974.
scattered in the 1940's
Swainson, John Burley, 1925-
Apr. 8, 1959, Jan. 17, 1961, July 11, 1961
Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.
Nov. 12, 1952
Tuttle, Arthur J., 1868-1944.
Oct. 8, 1944, Aug. 26, 1935
Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
Sept. 7, 1929
Van Wagoner, Murray Delos, 1898-
Mar. 3, 1933, Mar. 9, 1933, Feb. 10, 1933, Feb. 11, 1933, Apr. 19, 1933.Mar. 16, 1933, May 25, 1933, Apr. 15, 1936, July 27, 1936, July 28, 1936, July 30, 1936, July 30, 1937, Jan. 24, 1941, Sept. 12, 1941, Jan. 14, 1942, Feb. 25, 1942
Voelker, John D. (John Donaldson), 1903-
Nov. 24, 1959
Waite, John Barker, 1882-
Oct. 17, 1947, Nov. 3, 1948
Walker, Moses L.
1930's
Warren, Earl, 1891-1974.
Mar. 19, 1956, Mar. 29, 1956, July 15, 1957, Oct. 20, 1958, May 11, 1961
Whittaker, Alfred Heacock, 1894-
1950's
Williams, G. Mennen, 1911-
Aug. 16, 1939, Aug. 24, 1939, Nov. 22, 1939, Jan. 17, 1940, Mar. 8, 1947, Mar. 25, 1947, May 29, 1948, Apr. 11, 1950, Dec. 13, 1950, Jan. 17, 1952, June 5, 1952, June 24, 1952, Apr. 8, 1953, Apr. 9, 1953, Sept. 28, 1953
May 3, 1954, Aug. 24, 1954, July 27, 1955, Nov. 9, 1955, Nov. 26, 1955, May 7, 1956, May 31, 1956, June 12, 1956, June 28, 1956, Apr. 30, 1957, May 29, 1957, June 17, 1957, July 8 1957, (to E. Bumgardner), July 18, 1957, Sept. 17, 1957, Nov. 5, 1957
Mar. 24, 1958, Apr. 1, 1958, June 12, 1958, July 2, 1958, Aug. 26, 1958, Oct. 21, 1958, Nov. 19, 1958, Dec. 22, 1958, (secretary), Jan. 6, 1959, Feb. 11, 1959, Feb. 24, 1959, Apr. 8, 1959, Apr. 27, 1959, Sept, 1, 1959, Sept. 24, 1959, Nov. 10, 1959, Nov. 16, 1959, Dec. 7, 1959, Jan. 22, 1960, Mar. 23, 1960, May 26, 1961, July 13, 1961
Williams, G. Mennen, Mrs.
Oct. 13, 1958, Feb. 4, 1959
Yost, Fielding Harris, 1871-1946.
June 6, 1941